[
  {
    "name": "mígheanasach",
    "prefix": "os comhair",
    "article": "an",
    "articleMut": "an",
    "noun": "daba",
    "nounMutFront": "daba",
    "nounMutMid": "",
    "nounMutBack": "aba",
    "adjective": "mígheanasach",
    "adjMutFront": "m",
    "adjMutMid": "hígheanasaigh",
    "adjMutBack": ""
  },
  {
    "name": "urghnách",
    "prefix": "i gcóir",
    "article": "an",
    "articleMut": "an",
    "noun": "loingeas",
    "nounMutFront": "l",
    "nounMutMid": "oingis",
    "nounMutBack": "",
    "adjective": "urghnách",
    "adjMutFront": "urghnách",
    "adjMutMid": "",
    "adjMutBack": "rghnách"
  },
  {
    "name": "inbhuailte",
    "prefix": "i ndiaidh",
    "article": "an",
    "articleMut": "an",
    "noun": "dingín",
    "nounMutFront": "dingín",
    "nounMutMid": "",
    "nounMutBack": "ingín",
    "adjective": "inbhuailte",
    "adjMutFront": "inbhuailte",
    "adjMutMid": "",
    "adjMutBack": "nbhuailte"
  },
  {
    "name": "treallach",
    "prefix": "i gcóir",
    "article": "",
    "articleMut": "",
    "noun": "foscripteanna",
    "nounMutFront": "foscripteanna",
    "nounMutMid": "",
    "nounMutBack": "oscripteanna",
    "adjective": "treallacha",
    "adjMutFront": "treallacha",
    "adjMutMid": "",
    "adjMutBack": "reallacha"
  },
  {
    "name": "foircneach",
    "prefix": "in aice",
    "article": "",
    "articleMut": "",
    "noun": "sméideoga",
    "nounMutFront": "sméideog",
    "nounMutMid": "",
    "nounMutBack": "",
    "adjective": "foircneacha",
    "adjMutFront": "foircneach",
    "adjMutMid": "",
    "adjMutBack": ""
  }
]